WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN)
Right here right now (burn)
kewashii shura no michi no naka
down a difficult road filled with endless struggles
hito no chizu wo hirogete doko e yuku
where do you think you are going following someone else's map?
gokusaishoku no karasu ga sore wo ubaitotte yaburisuteta
an insightful crow comes along to tear up the map
saa kokoro no me mihiraite shika to ima wo mikiwamero (YEAH)
Now open your eyes and take a look at the truth (yeah)
ushinau mono nante nai sa iza mairou
there's nothing to lose, so let's go
WE ARE FIGHTING DREAMERS takami wo mezashite
we are Fighting Dreamers aiming high
FIGHTING DREAMERS narifuri kamawazu
Fighting Dreamers, don't care what people think about them
FIGHTING DREAMERS shinjiru ga mama ni
Fighting Dreamers, follow what they believe
OLI OLI OLI OH JUST GO MY WAY
oli oli oli oh! just go my way
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase LIKE A dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BANG) buppanase Like a dangan LINER
right here right now (bang) hit it straight like a line drive
RIGHT HERE RIGHT NOW (BURN) buttagitteku ze GET THE FIRE BANG
right here right now (burn) let's slash right through and get the fire, bang!
I've done it!
The water is turning!
It seems it's going to be easier
than I thought to break it.
Then I'll go take a little rest
until it's done... with this.
Hey! What is that?!
I need it to kill time.
And also to get some sleep.
Huh! The way it's going,
it won't even be an afternoon nap!
Is that so...?
Call me when it is broken.
Just wait!
If it keeps up like this,
I'll learn it within today!
Guts!!!
Pop, Water Balloon!
Oh man! Why doesn't it break!
Huh? Are you done with it?
Ah... well, it's almost done
or how should I call it.
Oh boy...
It seems like I went beyond
an afternoon nap and had a deep sleep.
Hey, hey... how do I break it?
Didn't I tell you I can't give
a detailed explanation until it's broken?
All right, I understand...
Naturally, you're supposed to realize it
through trial and error
when mastering a Jutsu, but...
Yeah, yeah.
I guess I'll teach you just
a tiny bit on the Jutsu...
You, try rotating the water!
Oh, okay.
Right or left... which direction did you
imagine when you rotate it?
Hmm... well, to the left...
Hey, come over here.
Okay...
Huh, I thought so...
W-What?
You are in fact a right-rotation type.
Right?
In order to build up Chakra,
it is necessary to blend the energy...
Chakra... Spiritual energy... Physical energy...
So everybody
unconsciously builds up Chakra
inside the body by rotating it.
Right... Left... Whether the rotation at
that point is to the right or to the left
differs in the individual.
Therefore, if you imagine
the rotation of the water balloon
opposite to that of your rotation-type
in this training,
your Chakra flow divides and resists
and the momentum of
the rotation does not get on track.
You should be able to figure
that kind of stuff on your own.
But how did you figure out that
I'm a right-type so fast?
The cowlick on your head!
It's pretty much determined that you're
a right type if a whorl rolls to the right
and you're a left-type
if it rolls to the left.
It's simple.
Huh, so I have a right roll!
Yes, so if you want to rotate it,
you have to imagine a right rotation.
I never really paid attention
to that until now...
But this Jutsu is just the one for you.
Hand sign is completely unnecessary.
All you need is Chakra.
There is no need to learn
a finicky hand sign!
It's okay to be stupid!
I'm not stupid!
I'm the man who's eventually going
to become Hokage!
It's easy once you understand!
This Jutsu, I'll completely master it
if I got three days!
Three days, huh?
This Jutsu is a Ninjutsu
that the Fourth Hokage passed on to us.
Huh...?
It took him three whole years
to perfect this Jutsu...
This Jutsu is second from the top
on the six degrees of
difficulty in mastering...
It's an A-rank, super high-level Ninjutsu.
In order to learn this move,
there are three steps in the training.
This "Water Balloon Breaking"
is the first step.
It took the genius Ninja,
the Fourth Hokage...
Three years...
There's no point in explaining
anymore to someone
who can't even clear the first step.
Do the rest by yourself!
Take care!
I'm going to return to the town.
I have to gather some information...
What will you do?
A-rank in degree of difficulty
in mastering...
The Ninjutsu left behind
by the Fourth Hokage...
I'm not gonna go back yet!
Huh...
So long... Don't go overboard with it.
Now, what will happen?
It's something to be concerned about...
Mister!
Why don't you stop by?
This month is our special service month.
Whoa! It's a special service month?
The more you visit,
the more you benefit.
Here you go, a stamp card!
I'll give you lots and lots of service!
I'll come, I'll come!
Hey! Come on down, Shu!
Hey, hey, where is the toilet?
I don't have time to spend three years.
All right now!
Training, once again today!
I'm gonna work hard like a blaze!
Break! Break! Break!
Why won't it break?
Jira-chan, you're so naughty!
Men are all naughty!
Damn it!
Three days have passed since
I got the tip from that Pervy Sage...
The rubber is stretched this much,
but why won't it break?
What am I doing different from
that Pervy Sage?
This is great! This is so great!
What the...?
Whoa, he stinks of alcohol.
I'm gonna eat now!
Huh?
What's the matter?
Oh, damn it!
Damn it! Why is it like this?!
No need to learn a finicky hand sign!
It's okay to be stupid!
He said that there's no need to form
a hand signal, but...
Hey! That's not your toy...
This is it!
Hurry up and wake up!
Hey, you Pervy Sage!
Uh... G-Good timing.
Why don't you bring me some water...
Water?
The first step is cleared!
Cleared...?
Well, let's have you show it to me.
All right! Watch it carefully!
Left hand?
Go!
All right! See that?! See that?!
You're sleeping!
Sorry, sorry.
I'm tired from the days and nights
of gathering information.
But that seems suspicious to begin with!
You still stink of alcohol too!
Nevertheless...
You rotate the water inside the water
balloon that you hold in your left hand
by repeatedly applying it
with your right hand...
It seems little strange of an idea, but...
You're an interesting kid.
You understood the trick pretty well.
It's all thanks to me, though.
It's thanks to this guy!
Huh?
I realized after I saw this cat playing
with the water balloon.
He kept on flicking it with
his paw many times
and the water inside shocked
in all different kinds of direction...
Then it came to me like "bingo"!
How did it come like "bingo"?
The time when the Pervy Sage
first showed me breaking it...
I remembered how the water balloon
surface was not smooth.
Until then,
I was always only rotating the water
in the one same direction...
I realized that the Pervy Sage's
water balloon was not smooth
because the water inside was rotating
in different directions.
And after doing it in my own way,
it broke!
It seems it's still not possible for you
to rotate it violently with one hand, but...
I suppose you thought it out
in your own way.
That's just what he expected of me!
Anyhow...
The first step is complete for now.
All right!
Do you want to see it one more time?
One more time!
Ow!
You used too much Chakra and
it gradually reached the point
where there's burden
on the Chakra Network...
But the next one won't be like this!
Okay. Now, we will proceed
to the second step.
Yeah!
It seems like we can finally go
into some serious training!
— Here you go!
— Huh?
Rubber ball?
Something like this again?!
Now, you'll break this one!
It's one hundred times harder
than the water balloon!
It's hard...
The first step is rotation,
the second step is force.
Since there is no water inside,
it's more difficult to imagine
the rotation of Chakra,
so it becomes more difficult
to rotate the Chakra as well.
That's true...
I'll leave that to your own judgment.
I need to learn a trick again
to do this, don't I?
Well then,
I'll go gather some information.
Hey! Wait, wait!
Let's train together for
the first time in a while!
I don't mind if you take a nap.
Don't depend on me!
You must have some kind
of misunderstanding!
I did say that I'll teach you the Jutsu,
but I don't have the obligation
to teach you every step of the way.
If you can't do it by yourself,
then that's it.
Don't be childish forever...
Become more respectable like a Shinobi!
Well, well then.
If you can at least teach me...
the trick again...
Money!
Money... money... money...
W-What do you mean
"be respectable like a Shinobi"?!
Even though you say that,
you're a dirty and greedy adult!
You're not a respectable Shinobi at all!
It's way more difficult than
the time with the water balloon...
A-And...
my hands and arms hurt.
Damn it! How many days am I
going to be doing the same thing!
Second from the top in
the difficulty of mastering...
Don't depend on me!
You must have some kind
of misunderstanding!
Damn it!
Hey, Naruto.
What did you come here for?
Go buy some food from the town below.
What?! Why me?
Hey you...
Even if for a while, you're still
learning the Jutsu from me.
Here you go, thanks for waiting.
Thank you.
How dare he put on a master's face
only at a time like this
when he doesn't teach me anything...
Dad, buy me some ice cream.
I want this one that cracks.
Here.
Why? I can eat all of it by myself.
Nope, when you get home,
your mother will have supper ready.
Okay!
Hey... you know...
Huh?
Can you be around my training
for just a while... today?
I don't have time for that.
I have to immediately go to town.
Unless you think for yourself and
get a grip of the trick for yourself,
it'll never work.
I thought I told you three weeks ago!
Don't be spoiled like a kid.
You are a Ninja.
I know that without
you telling me!
Just thought I'd ask.
Hurry up and go,
you Pervy Sage!
Oh no, little Jira-chan,
you tell so many lies!
What do you mean?!
Everything is true!
Damn it! It doesn't break
no matter how much I try...
I'm just dripping away
my Chakra this way.
Also...
The more I increase the amount of flow,
the worse the pain gets.
But... How do I say it?
If I don't go all out as if
to explode the Chakra,
it's not going to break!
That's it!
If I understand the amount of Chakra
that flows from the pain I feel...
Then I can bear the pain to the limit
and all at once...
No, not yet...
Not yet!
Not yet... store it!
Now!
Ow!
Hmm... There seems to have been
a little progress.
Humph!
I've still only opened a hole
and it hasn't popped with a bang!
Hey, don't pretend to be so tough. Here!
You've done well,
all on your own power.
It's so good!
Yes...
Oh yeah. Maybe we'll test a bit.
What, what?
Give me your right hand.
What's this?
gaman no renzoku dattaro
a cycle of hardship, right?
kokoro de naiteita ndarou
inside, we were crying, right?
jibun de kimeta sono yume dake wa yuzurenai ndarou
but the one thing we won't give up is the dream we've chosen, right?
wakiyaku dakedo
it's a secondary role
kage no hito dakedo
a role in the shadows
yume to mukiau toki kurai
but in reaching for that dream
man naka ni isasete shoujiki ni isasete
let us stay centered, let us stay true
ima made nandomo nan toka akiramezu ni
over and over, we hung on without giving up
ima made nandomo tachi agatte kita janai ka
over and over, we kept coming back up
ima made nandomo
over and over, we believed and dreamed
bokura
nandomo
shinjite
yume mite nandomo
ima made nandomo baka o mite kita janai ka
over and over, we've seen fools
ima made nandomo hito no kage ni tatte kita janai ka
over and over, we've stood in the shadows of others
saa shuyaku da yo jibun no yume kurai wagamama de isasete
now, it's our turn... let us bask in our dreams
He tells me
"focus, focus, focus!"
But I've never been good at it, ever.
Speaking of concentration,
Iruka-sensei used to scold me often
at the Ninja Academy
for my lack of concentration.
Oh... I would've listened to him better
if I knew this would happen.
Next time:
"The Konoha Mark and Forehead Protector."